<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>faq on Soluspay | Secure Payments</title>
    <link>/tags/faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in faq on Soluspay | Secure Payments</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pin block calculations for EBS</title>
      <link>/post/pin_block/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pin_block/</guid>
      <description>In financial transactions, pin block calculations is one of the most important tasks and it&amp;rsquo;s often a source for mistakes. In this article, we will be discussing pin block calculations in EBS system (it uses DES) while using our implementation, TA. TA is written in Python and it is used internally by our team for all of our testing and pin calculations. The source code is also available in Github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ: your first support for any EBS issue</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>List of common EBS errors and their meaninings    error code error meaning how to solve     196 System error regarding the pin block see our post on pin block calculations   000 Approval    103 Format Error Invalid merchant or service provider   130 Invalid format The transaction has invalid format. After the transaction authorization, the terminal or external host will declined the response   178 Original request not found Returned if the voucher is not found for the particular phone number sent on the request of cash out voucher, the phone number entered isn’t the same as the one used to generate the voucher   158 Invalid processing code    161 Withdrawal limit exceeded    191 Destination not available The transaction destination (e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>